foreign
[Music]
we always use technology to Foster
Innovation and to deliver on our
strategic goals
but along with delivering our strategy
we also need to look at our culture and
people practices
famously said culture eats strategy for
breakfast diversity equity and inclusion
are di for short is what we want to
really emphasize as a part of our
cultural values we need to have teams
with individuals from different
backgrounds because that's what brings
about diversity of viewpoint important
ingredient for fostering Innovation it's
also necessary that each of these
members gets the equality of opportunity
all members in the team should have
atmosphere where they feel welcome to
contribute and participate in the team
but I think time has come that we need
to amplify this be more vocal about it
we need to speak up about it to practice
and encourage this it's only when we
really have da as an ingrained part of
our culture at ICS Lombard that we can
become a truly adaptive resilient and
Innovative organization
foreign
spots are visible to everybody a lot of
audience that is out there which we need
to grow and sell products to and a lot
of audience which is available to hire
both are going to be more and more
diverse As Time professors
and if we want to be able to attract
them retain them either as customers or
as employees we definitely need to make
strides in being more diverse whether it
is gender or age or age or religion or
region more than about 50 of women are
graduating out of colleges what is
required is to put a structure in
getting more women in to the fold
because then we will reach a place where
we are able to create a balance of
numbers of representation of women so
that we can cater more to the women
customers are there in the market and
create a more uh familiar place for The
Women Within the company as well we need
to be more Equitable which is that we
provide what we need to become
successful where we do not compromise
and be inclusive which is provide the
culture that they need to thrive and
stay with us
if you look at uh you know the Journey
of ICS Lombard you know it's been 21
years for us and we have achieved a lot
in a short span of windy audios it is a
great time to look at ODI aspect you
know diversity Beauty and inclusion each
of these uh you know pillars would
really form a big foundation for the
future growth of the organization Dei
for me is about encouraging newer ideas
uh you know giving respect to diverse
views uh thereby fostering Innovation if
you look at any of these large Global uh
big organizations and companies who have
sustained and you know performed and
have been successful Beyond 100 years
150 to even 200 years they have had some
kind of a big focus on having a diverse
Workforce where we are now in that you
know threshold I believe that diversity
equity and inclusion can be a big
contributor to our next piece overall
foreign
[Music]
I think this would go a long way in
creating the talent pools within the
organization which would create a
culture of inclusiveness and lead to
employ engagement and Trust
being respectful and being respected
let's innovate we have practice
policies
foreign
thank you